# Morris Ifeanyi IGWE

### **Demand Planner**

I have over 18 years of professional working experience in oil and gas, energy and agriculture sector including 10 years' strong work experience in Supply Chain-with specific focus on inventory management, expediting, logistics and Procure to Pay. I have over the years of my career developed the capability to work with high motivated team in other to meet organizational goals. I am always ready to relocate and meet new challenging roles. I have an in-depth knowledge on operations and project Management in energy, oil and gas, Research and rural development project delivery, supply-chain and logistics processes.



Morris.igwe@montzenergy.com



https://github.com/Morrisig



7a Godson Ilodianya Close, Oniru, Lekki, Lagos State

## **WORK EXPERIENCE**

#### **Demand Planner**

# Halliburton Energy Services Ltd 08/2016 - 07/2020

I was responsible in leading materials inventory planning requirements for all Halliburton departments to help provide seamless integration of Supply Chain operations and processes. I collaborate with Departments and Business Development (BD) staff, manufacturing personnel, internal and external suppliers, and logistics personnel to ensure inventory levels meet business requirements. I also ensure inventory planning is appropriate to minimize surplus inventory and control costs. I am responsible for planning activities including review of forecasts generated by inventory planning tools, ensuring that regular inventory planning meetings are held and that actions arising from these meetings are executed. I am responsible for ensuring that planning processes are adhered to and that planning tools are used effectively. I am as well responsible for meeting financial goals and objectives for the business.

### Senior Materials Controls Specialist.

# Halliburton Energy Services Ltd 09/2013 – 07/2016

I was responsible for leading local inventory planning meetings, setting and maintenance of material requirements planning (MRP) data, running analytics to optimize inventory levels, and identifying and redeploying obsolete inventory. Responsible for the basic inventory management function for company and include: sales order delivery process and reconciliation, reporting to department leadership key metrics, goods issue and receiving process and developing solutions to address gaps. Will interface with procurement, logistics and manufacturing customer service representatives to prioritize orders, monitor lead times, and provide forecast information.

### **Operations Assistant-Downhole and Special Tools.**

Halliburton Energy Services Nigeria Limited.

August 2009-June 2013

I work with the operations coordinators and assists with pre-job product and service equipment preparation (assembly, test, mobilization), and with product installation at the well site. I actively participated with post-job demobilization, clean up, and repair of service equipment and products. I was responsible for field services deployments of tool and services in rigs and platforms, reporting and feedback to the operations management.

		-	_		
4	2	ı,		N	
	П	ľ	П		١
`			в	,	

https://www.linkedin.com/in/morris-igwe-jp-93053879/



07040390845

### **EDUCATION**

Bachelors of Science-B.Sc. Natural Sciences- Botany. Nnamdi Azikiwe University, Awka. 09/1998 - 05/2002

#### **TRAININGS**

1 Texas A&M University 07/2015 Business Development Leadership-BLD

2 Ministry of Agriculture, Israel-MOSHAV Program 07/2018 Agricultural Seeds Production

### **CERTIFICATES**

1 Scrum Master Professional 02/2021 Certiprof Inc. USA

DevOps Practitioner03/2021Global Skills Development Council-GSDC. USA

# Morris Ifeanyi IGWE

**Demand Planner** 

## **WORK EXPERIENCE**

#### **Services Planner-SAP OTC**

# Baroid Nigeria Limited (Halliburton Energy Services Ltd) 05/2006 - 03/2009

My job responsibility addressed a variety of administrative needs. I was the one stop shop for operational record keeping skills from cash orders, plant maintenance and to purchase records. I support service coordinators through specific processing of Order to Cash, Plant Maintenance and Procurement data entry and work BD-Business Development Teams on cost controls, contract issues and new project developments. I am responsible for daily inventory commitment and reconciliation and also work with resource planners on the vital tasks of job scheduling and dispatching of workers. I work with resource planners in maintaining accuracy of scheduling board and the dispatching of jobs in SAP and in resolving Assets and operational equipment scheduling issues.

## SKILLS

Agile Scum Master	Agile Product Owner	
DevOps Practitioner	SAP End Users	
Supply Chain	Inventory Management	
Business Analyst	MS Office Tools	
LEAN	Forecasting	
Collaboration Tools	Operations Planning	